#### Contact

mohitkumar51k@gmail.com LinkedIn Profile

### Top Skills · See all

Microsoft Office · Customer Service · Microsoft Excel · Microsoft Word · Data Entry · KYC · Data Cleaning · Research · Project Management · Typing

# **Mohit Panchal**

Data Analyst at iTech Creators Pvt. Ltd.

New Delhi, Delhi, India

### Summary

Data entry professionals work either as individuals or as part of a larger team. Most of their day is spent analyzing data and entering it into spreadsheets or content management systems. These professionals often work from a home office and are proficient with productivity suite software like Good knowledge of MS-Word, MS-Excel and Data Entry & Web Research Data Cleaning ...

Read more

## Experience

Data Analyst · iTech Creators Pvt. Ltd.

July 2019 - Present · India

At [digitechnique] we count on meticulously accurate and insightful data to drive our solutions. We are currently looking for a highly skilled data entry specialist with exceptional detail orientation and analytical skill to join us in our mission.- Daily and Monthly Responsibilities Gather and input data into

KYC Executive · InstantPay

February 2018 - May 2019 (1 year 4 months) · New Delhi Area, India

#### Education

## Government Industrial Training Institute - India

Mechanical Engineering/Mechanical Technology/Technician · (2017 - 2018)